<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Bugnet</string>
    <string name="help">\tThis is a simple app, that helps manual testers
        to create visual bug reports.
        To create you first bug report:\n\n
        \t1) Take some screenshots with your device. For example, if your device
        manufacturer is "Samsung", you should press "Power" and "home" button
        in the same time, to take screenshots.\n\n
        \t2) Open app and press "Edit captured screenshots" button. You should see an empty page.\n\n
        \t3) Press menu button.\n\n
        \t4) Press add screenshots button. You will see a pop up, where you can select
        your gallery app.\n\n
        \t5) Choose your screenshot with gallery. You can choose other images, but
        please keep in mind that this an alpha version.\n\n
        \t6) Add all screenshots, that needed.\n\n
        \t7) Press on the image to draw on them. You can save your drawings by pressing
        back button.\n\n
        \t8) Press on the "Step" text to change the description. You can choose one of
        presented phrases or type it manually with "add description button"\n\n
        \t9) Press menu button. You can add bug report description and additional
        information with listed menu options.\n\n
        \t10) Press menu button. Press "generate report" button to create bug report.\n\n
        \t11) Then bug report was created, you can use "view report" button on the main
        page. You will be able to view html web page with html viewer or with your web
        browser.\n\n
        \t12) Press "get system info", if you want to add system information to your
        report. You will be redirected to the play market, where you can download an
        app, that will allow you to access to system information.\n\n
        \t13) Press share button to send your report via email.\n\n
        \t14) Press menu button on the main screen.\n\n
        \t15) Press "empty workflow" button to clear your workflow. It will delete
        files only in app directory, all your images will stay where they are.\n\n
        \t16) *For rooted phones. If your device have root access, you will be able
        to use additional feature. Press menu button. Press touch detection. You will
        see a small overlay screen in the left top side of your screen with three
        buttons. "SC" button will take a screenshot of your screen. "SW" button will
        change overlay position and "HD" button will hide overlay screen. It will
        appear again if you will press again on the hidden overlay.\n\n
        Happy testing:)\n</string>
    <string name="main_menu_start">Start touch detection</string>
	<string name="main_menu_stop">Stop touch detection</string>
	

</resources>
